MUHAMMAD ANAS AFZAAL

B-185 Saghir Centre, Block-16 F.B Area, Karachi. phone: +(92)312 3616359 email: anaskhan.all95@gmail.com

WORK EXPERIENCE

Front end Developer – Symits (September 2020 – Present)

My JD involves development, optimization, and, maintenance of websites of several scales using latest technologies such as HTML, CSS, JavaScript, Bootstrap, PHP, jQuery, WordPress, Shopify and, Adobe Photoshop to name a few.

Front end Developer – Optimal Creations (March 2020 – August 2020)

My duties included development, optimization, and maintenance of websites using technologies such as HTML, CSS, JavaScript, WordPress, and Shopify to name a few. My J.D also involved writing content for social media and other websites. I have also served as the editor for CEO of Optimal Creations, Mr. Sarmad Ali Abbasi's book, 'Unboxing the Phenomenal World of Digital Marketing'.

EDUCATION

- Masters of Computer Science (MCS) University of Karachi (February 2021– Present)
- ➤ Bachelors of Computer Science (BCS) University of Karachi (February 2016 December 2018)
- ➤ Intermediate D.J Science College (February 2016 December 2018)
- Matriculation Metropolitan Academy (April 1999 February 2012)

SUMMARY

I am a Frontend Developer who understands and manages the user interface according to the users' needs and the best of the experience.

I have core expertise in the latest technologies and trends such as HTML, CSS, JavaScript, jQuery, React JS, React Native, PHP, WordPress, C#, SQL name a few.

LINKS

Portfolio

LinkedIn:

SKILLS

avaScript:	
React JS:	
React Native:	
Query:	
PHP:	_
MySQL:	_
C#:	_
SQL:	_
Git:	
HTML:	
CSS:	
Mard Procs.	